Sound of My Voice is a science fiction, drama,
mystery film directed by Zal Batmanglij.
A journalist and his girlfriend get pulled in while they investigate
a cult whose leader claims to be from the future.
Maggie, played by Brit Marling.
Peter Aitken, played by Christopher Denham.
Lorna Michaelson, played by Nicole Vicius.
Carol Briggs, played by Davenia McFadden.
Joanne, played by Kandice Stroh.
Klaus, played by Richard Wharton.
Sound of My Voice is a 2011 American psychological thriller film
directed by Zal Batmanglij in his feature directorial debut.
The screenplay was written by Batmanglij and Brit Marling, and the film
stars Christopher Denham, Nicole Vicius, and Marling.
The plot focuses on two documentary filmmakers who infiltrate a cult led
by a charismatic woman who claims to be from the future.
The film premiered at the 2011 Sundance Film Festival and was
also selected to close the 2011 SXSW Film Festival.
It was released by Fox Searchlight Pictures on April 27, 2012.
The film explores themes of journalist,
manipulation, hidden camera, teacher, school.
The tone is dark and emotional and mind_bending.